<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE dialogue[<!ATTLIST node id ID #IMPLIED>]>
<dialogue>
    <intro>
        <text>A pleasant aura surrounds this man. He seems eager to speak to you.</text>
        <next_node id="1" />
    </intro>
    <topic id="serum">
        <title>Serum</title>
        <next_node id="12" />
    </topic>
    <node id="12">
        <response>
            <condition name="zsk_hans_has_brain" story="zsk_hans_has_brain" compare="0" op="0" />
            <text>I haven't made a lot of progress on them. But they sound interesting! Save lives, make money, win-win right? I really want to look into it, but you see, I'm no ghoul hunter, just some clumsy egghead, so I have no test subjects. It would be nice if we had some ghouls in captivity...</text>
        </response>
        <response>
            <condition name="zsk_hans_has_brain" story="zsk_hans_has_brain" compare="1" op="0" />
            <text>I have some serum for sale, if you want.</text>
        </response>
        <option>
            <logic type="And">
                <condition name="zsk_know_artyom" story="zsk_know_artyom" compare="1" op="0" />
                <condition name="zsk_hans_has_brain" story="zsk_hans_has_brain" compare="0" op="0" />
            </logic>
            <title>Artyom</title>
            <text>There is an infected man called Artyom locked up in the cellar. He's about to turning into a ghoul.</text>
            <next_node id="13" />
        </option>
    </node>
    <node id="13">
        <response>
            <text>Ah, yes! I forgot about him. He makes a great test subject because his brain is in-between human and ghoul state, which is very useful for finding out how the transition works. So, the brain...</text>
        </response>
        <option>
            <title>Brain</title>
            <text>What about his brain?</text>
            <next_node id="14" />
        </option>
    </node>
    <node id="14">
        <response>
            <text>I need you to get it for me. Go put him out of his misery and bring me the brain. Be careful - the brain must be intact for my research. Don't ruin it. </text>
            <event name="zsk_hans_asked_for_brain" />
        </response>
        <option>
            <title>Research</title>
            <text>What research are you doing with his brain?</text>
            <next_node id="15" />
        </option>
    </node>
    <node id="15">
        <response>
            <text>I'm making a serum that can temporarily protect you from the Visitation. </text>
        </response>
    </node>
    <node id="1">
        <response>
            <text>Good day! What brings you here?</text>
        </response>
        <option>
            <logic type="And">
                <condition name="zsk_sid_quest" story="zsk_sid_quest" compare="3" op="1" />
                <condition name="zsk_hans_quest" story="zsk_hans_quest" compare="0" op="0" />
            </logic>
            <title>Help</title>
            <text>Sidorovich said you needed some help.</text>
            <next_node id="2" />
        </option>
        <option>
            <logic type="And">
                <condition name="zsk_has_priest_book" story="zsk_has_priest_book" compare="1" op="0" />
                <condition name="zsk_hans_quest" story="zsk_hans_quest" compare="1" op="0" />
            </logic>
            <title>Document</title>
            <text>I found this journal in the church.</text>
            <next_node id="9" />
        </option>
        <option>
            <condition name="zsk_has_artyom_brain" story="zsk_has_artyom_brain" compare="1" op="0" />
            <title>Artyom's Brain</title>
            <text>I got you Artyom's brain.</text>
            <next_node id="16" />
        </option>
    </node>
    <node id="2">
        <response>
            <text>Ah, yes! I appreciate your offer. I'm working on a device, a detector that can warn you before you step into an anomaly. And my intention is simple - I just want to make some money selling it, to be honest.</text>
        </response>
        <option>
            <title>Continue</title>
            <text>Interesting.</text>
            <next_node id="3" />
        </option>
    </node>
    <node id="3">
        <response>
            <text>Building this device is not easy, though. First I needed money to buy components. I got help from folks in Zernaskaya - they each gave me some money and in return I'll give them the device for free. I call it "crowd funding", you see?</text>
        </response>
        <option>
            <title>Money</title>
            <text>So you need money from me?</text>
            <next_node id="4" />
        </option>
    </node>
    <node id="4">
        <response>
            <text>No, not money - that has been taken care of. I need data. Each anomaly is different and the detector must posess a set of parameters for each type of anomaly to detect it. There used to be a man whom they called "The Priest", I heard that he did some research on the anomalies.</text>
        </response>
        <option>
            <title>The Priest</title>
            <text>Who's The Priest?</text>
            <next_node id="5" />
        </option>
    </node>
    <node id="5">
        <response>
            <text>He was a legend, and there are a lot of stories about him. You can ask around the camp and people will tell you all about him. But he hasn't been seen or heard from since last year.</text>
            <event name="zsk_learn_priest" />
        </response>
        <option>
            <title>Continue</title>
            <text>I see.</text>
            <next_node id="6" />
        </option>
    </node>
    <node id="6">
        <response>
            <text>I don't know why they call him "The Priest", but I guess it's because he lived in the church. I believe he has some documents there of his study. If you could retrieve the documents for me, that will really help with my progress.</text>
        </response>
        <option>
            <title>Sure</title>
            <text>Sure, I can do that for you.</text>
            <next_node id="8" />
        </option>
        <option>
            <title>Not right now</title>
            <text>Not at this time, I'm busy with something else.</text>
            <next_node id="7" />
        </option>
    </node>
    <node id="8">
        <response>
            <text>Terrific! The church is northwest of the village, near the barn house. Be careful though, that area is infested with Ghouls.</text>
            <event name="zsk_hans_find_doc_begin" />
        </response>
    </node>
    <node id="7">
        <response>
            <text>No problem! Let me know if you change your mind.</text>
        </response>
    </node>
    <node id="9">
        <response>
            <text>Let me see! Hmm, a lot of text about his spirituality struggles. He did run into several anomalies, here and there, and lived to tell the tale. Good, I'll study the journal more, and I'll let you know when I make further progress with my detector. So thank you! By the way, was there anything anomalous inside the church?</text>
            <event name="zsk_hans_find_doc_done" />
        </response>
        <option>
            <title>Nothing</title>
            <text>I didn't see anything abnormal.</text>
            <next_node id="11" />
        </option>
        <option>
            <title>Anomaly</title>
            <text>I saw a floating orb that shoots out eletric bolts to metal objects.</text>
            <next_node id="10" />
        </option>
    </node>
    <node id="11">
        <response>
            <text>That would be odd. The church door was sealed, so there must be something dangerous inside!</text>
        </response>
    </node>
    <node id="10">
        <response>
            <text>Interesting. Alright, I will add a sensor that can detect ionized air particles.</text>
        </response>
    </node>
    <node id="16">
        <response>
            <text>Let me have a look... Aha! This is the missing link to my serum! Well thanks to you, now we have a better chance to live through future Visitations. Artyom's sacrifice was not in vain. Here, you can have a sample of the serum, and you can buy more from me if you need it.</text>
            <event name="zsk_hans_got_brain" />
        </response>
    </node>
</dialogue>