<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE dialogue[<!ATTLIST node id ID #IMPLIED>]>
<dialogue>
    <intro>
        <text></text>
        <next_node id="1" />
    </intro>
    <topic id="zsk_blockade">
        <title>Blockade</title>
        <next_node id="2" />
    </topic>
    <node id="2">
        <response>
            <condition name="zsk_sid_quest" story="zsk_sid_quest" compare="1" op="0" />
            <text>Blockade has been lifted for you, good luck!</text>
        </response>
        <response>
            <logic type="And">
                <condition name="zsk_village_gate_open" story="zsk_village_gate_open" compare="0" op="0" />
                <condition name="zsk_sid_quest" story="zsk_sid_quest" compare="0" op="0" />
            </logic>
            <text>Well yes, we have decided to temporarily close the gate for new comers. But that's only because we need help. </text>
        </response>
        <option>
            <logic type="And">
                <condition name="zsk_village_gate_open" story="zsk_village_gate_open" compare="0" op="0" />
                <condition name="zsk_sid_quest" story="zsk_sid_quest" compare="0" op="0" />
            </logic>
            <title>Help</title>
            <text>What can I do to help?</text>
            <next_node id="3" />
        </option>
    </node>
    <node id="3">
        <response>
            <text>Let's make a deal. I got three jobs that needs to be done, and nobody around here has the balls to do any of them. I can't send Razor because he's the chief of my guards; and let's just be direct - these jobs can get you killed, and I can't afford to lose Razor. But if you get these jobs done for me - and I don't care how you do it - not only will I let you through my gate, but I'll also guide you deeper into the zone. What do you think?</text>
        </response>
        <option>
            <title>Yes</title>
            <text>Alright, let's hear it.</text>
            <next_node id="4" />
        </option>
        <option>
            <title>Not yet</title>
            <text>I'll think about it.</text>
            <next_node id="5" />
        </option>
    </node>
    <node id="4">
        <response>
            <text>Good! Here's the first job: right outside the village, up north, there is a barn which we have been using to grow potatoes. We hate eating potatoes but we use them to produce alcohol.</text>
        </response>
        <option>
            <title>Continue</title>
            <text>Go on.</text>
            <next_node id="6" />
        </option>
    </node>
    <node id="6">
        <response>
            <text>You see, the alcohol is our main trade - the eggheads among the mutant hunters pay a lot of dough for it, and that's how we've been surviving. But recently a bunch of assholes who call themselves "Legionaires" raided our farm and took it for themselves, along with all the distillers. And that puts us in some deep shit. </text>
        </response>
        <option>
            <title>Continue</title>
            <text>I see. So you need me to take it back for you, right?</text>
            <next_node id="7" />
        </option>
    </node>
    <node id="7">
        <response>
            <text>Exactly. Get rid of the Legionaires; and if you can, check on the potatoes for us, they probably haven't been watered for a long time. The farm is directly north from the village, on the other side of the hill. I'll go head and tell Razor to let you through the gate. Now grab your gun and get to it!</text>
            <event name="zsk_village_exit_unlock" />
        </response>
        <option>
            <title>Guns</title>
            <text>Do you have some guns for me?</text>
            <next_node id="8" />
        </option>
    </node>
    <node id="8">
        <response>
            <text>No, I don't. What the hell are you doing in the zone without a shooter?</text>
        </response>
    </node>
    <node id="5">
        <response>
            <text>Alright, take your time.</text>
        </response>
    </node>
    <topic id="your_story">
        <title>Story</title>
        <next_node id="9" />
    </topic>
    <node id="9">
        <response>
            <text>I'm a business man. As such, I hate adventures. Now, adventure and risk are totally different things. I take risks, which is why I'm here in this God forsaken place. My son, on the other hand, is completely the opposite.</text>
        </response>
        <option>
            <title>Your Son</title>
            <text>Where is your son?</text>
            <next_node id="10" />
        </option>
    </node>
    <node id="10">
        <response>
            <text>He lives in Kiev. He wanted to come here with me, but I didn't let him. He's a man of hot-headed adventures and he'll get himself killed here. </text>
        </response>
    </node>
    <topic id="zsk_farm_clear">
        <title>Farm</title>
        <next_node id="12" />
    </topic>
    <node id="12">
        <response>
            <text>Did you get our brewery back?</text>
        </response>
        <option>
            <logic type="And">
                <condition name="zsk_barn_cleared" story="zsk_barn_cleared" compare="1" op="0" />
                <condition name="zsk_barn_water_on" story="zsk_barn_water_on" compare="0" op="0" />
            </logic>
            <title>Farm</title>
            <text>I cleared the farm for you.</text>
            <next_node id="11" />
        </option>
        <option>
            <logic type="And">
                <condition name="zsk_barn_cleared" story="zsk_barn_cleared" compare="1" op="0" />
                <condition name="zsk_barn_water_on" story="zsk_barn_water_on" compare="1" op="0" />
            </logic>
            <title>Farm</title>
            <text>The farm is clear, and I turned on the irrigators too.</text>
            <next_node id="11" />
        </option>
    </node>
    <node id="11">
        <response>
            <condition name="zsk_barn_water_on" story="zsk_barn_water_on" compare="0" op="0" />
            <text>Great! I'll send our boys to take over the farm. Are you ready for the next task?</text>
            <event name="zsk_barn_quest_done1" />
        </response>
        <response>
            <condition name="zsk_barn_water_on" story="zsk_barn_water_on" compare="1" op="0" />
            <text>Well done! You save us a lot of work. I'll send our boys to take over the farm. Here, they would want you to have this. Now, are you ready for the next task?</text>
            <event name="zsk_barn_quest_done2" />
        </response>
        <option>
            <title>Yes</title>
            <text>I'm ready.</text>
            <next_node id="13" />
        </option>
        <option>
            <title>No</title>
            <text>I need some time.</text>
            <next_node id="5" />
        </option>
    </node>
    <node id="13">
        <response>
            <text>Now that we got our brewery back, we need to deliver goods to our customers. No, that's not your job - you don't know the way around and our customers don't trust you.</text>
        </response>
        <option>
            <title>OK</title>
            <text>OK.</text>
            <next_node id="14" />
        </option>
    </node>
    <node id="14">
        <response>
            <text>For the past several months, the Legionnaires held the train station, so the only way out of Zernaskaya is through the sewers under the church. Since we haven't been there for a while, the whole area got overrun with ghouls. </text>
        </response>
        <option>
            <title>Ghouls</title>
            <text>What are these Ghouls?</text>
            <next_node id="15" />
        </option>
    </node>
    <node id="15">
        <response>
            <text>They are humans at the first stage of mutation after contracting the Tungus Complex. They aren't too dangerous individually, but if many of them gang up on you in a tight space, it's certain death. I need you to clear the Ghouls so we can use the underground sewer to transport goods out. Before you go, see if you can find Hans somewhere in the village. I heard he needed some help.</text>
            <event name="zsk_sid_church_begin" />
        </response>
    </node>
    <topic id="zsk_ivan_igor">
        <title>Ivan And Igor</title>
        <next_node id="16" />
    </topic>
    <node id="16">
        <response>
            <text>Yes, they are my transporters. Three weeks ago I sent them on a delivery but didn't hear from them since. </text>
        </response>
        <option>
            <condition name="zsk_read_ivan_note" story="zsk_read_ivan_note" compare="1" op="0" />
            <title>Death</title>
            <text>I found their dead bodies. They were killed by ghouls.</text>
            <next_node id="17" />
        </option>
    </node>
    <node id="17">
        <response>
            <text>Oh! What a shame. At least they didn't run away with my money, right? Were they carrying anything?</text>
        </response>
        <option>
            <title>Yes</title>
            <text>Yes, I found 190 rubles. Ivan asked to return them to you and send their savings to his mother.</text>
            <next_node id="18" />
        </option>
        <option>
            <title>No</title>
            <text>No, didn't find anything on them.</text>
            <next_node id="19" />
        </option>
    </node>
    <node id="18">
        <response>
            <condition name="zsk_has_ivan_money" story="zsk_has_ivan_money" compare="190" op="1" />
            <text>Hmm... Well seems like they are loyal boys after all. I'll send their savings out. And thank you for bringing the money back.</text>
            <event name="zsk_lose_ivan_money" />
        </response>
        <response>
            <condition name="zsk_has_ivan_money" story="zsk_has_ivan_money" compare="190" op="-2" />
            <text>You don't have the money. I'll just take whatever you have and use their savings to cover the rest.</text>
            <event name="zsk_lose_ivan_money" />
        </response>
    </node>
    <node id="19">
        <response>
            <text>Them bastards! I knew I couldn't trust them! Guess I'll just keep their savings to cover my loss.</text>
            <event name="zsk_forget_ivan" />
        </response>
    </node>
    <node id="1">
        <response>
            <text>Hey there, what can I do you for?</text>
        </response>
        <option>
            <condition name="zsk_sid_quest" story="zsk_sid_quest" compare="2" op="0" />
            <title>Next Job</title>
            <text>What's my next job?</text>
            <next_node id="13" />
        </option>
    </node>
</dialogue>